Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records and Photographs WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series II: Records of the Legislative Conference, 1926-1975
  - Affirmative Action, CUNY: General, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action, CUNY: General, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action/Discrimination: General, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Agreement with BHE, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Agreements, 1969, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Adelphi, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1958, 1962-1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 384 (BHE Employees), 1962-1963, 1965-1973, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - AFSCME, Local 2054, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Announcements, undated, 1959-1975 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Arbitrations, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Audits, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Bargaining, 1967-1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Baruch College, 1964-1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Baruch College: Discrimination, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Baruch School of Business, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Beck v. Teachers Retirement System, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Board of Higher Education, 1953-1966 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - BHE, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - BHE, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - BHE, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - BHE: Committee on Bylaws, 1962-1968 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - BHE: Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - BHE: Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - BHE: Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - BHE: Correspondence, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - BHE: Correspondence, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - BHE: Members' Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - BHE: Members' Correspondence, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - BHE: Members' Correspondence, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - BHE: Members' Correspondence, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - BHE: Special Committees on Governance, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Boston Bill (Library Service), 1966 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bronx Community College, 1954-1960 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Bronx Community College, 1961-1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn College, 1962-1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn College, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Brooklyn College: Sex Discrimination, 1962, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn College: Sex Discrimination, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Bulletins, 1954, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Bylaws Committee, 1959-1961, 1963-1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Canudo, Eugene, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Canudo, Eugene, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Canudo, Eugene, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Canudo, Eugene, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Canudo, Eugene, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Canudo, Eugene, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Certification Procedures, 1958, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Check-off, 1959, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Citizens Commission on the Future of CUNY, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - City and State Reports Filed, 1959-1961, 1965-1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - City College, 1961-1972 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - City College: Faculty Senate, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - CUNY: Administration, 1958-1969 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - CUNY: Administration, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - CUNY: Budget, 1963-1972 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - CUNY: Budget Crisis, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - CUNY: Central Office: Discrimination, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - CUNY: Faculty Senate, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - CUNY: Governance, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - CUNY: Governance, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - CUNY: Graduate Center, 1964-1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - CUNY: Sex Discrimination, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - CUNY: Student Senate, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - CUNY: University Senate, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Clancy Bill, 1964, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Collective Bargaining: Campaign, 1963-1972 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Collective Bargaining: Elections, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: General, 1962-1969 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: General, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: General, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Collective Bargaining: Petitions and Proposals, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - College Laboratory Technicians, 1961-1969 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - College Laboratory Technicians, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - College Science Associates, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Commission on Structure of NYC Government, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Discrimination against Women, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Education of Faculty Organization Bylaws, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Committee on School of General Studies, 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Status of Women, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Committees: Various, 1963-1971 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Community Colleges, 1958-1969 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Community Colleges, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Conference Leader, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Conklin-Ryan Bill, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Conklin-Ryan Bill: Prior Service Certificates, 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Conklin-Ryan Bill: Retirement Allowances, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Constitutional Convention (NYS), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Credit Rating Issue, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Council for Public Higher Education, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Directories, 1960-1967, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Due Process, undated, 1967-1971 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Dues, 1965, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Educational Planning Committee, 1960-1968 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Elections, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Evaluations, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Faculty Association News, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Power, ca.1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Finances, undated, 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Financial Reports, 1965, 1967-1972 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Governance: Chandler Report, 1969-1971, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Governing Board, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Governing Board: Agendas, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Grievance Committee, 1964-1972 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Grievance Committee Cases, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Grievances, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Grievances, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Heald Committee Report, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Higher Education Officers, 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - History, 1953-1971 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Hostos Community College, 1970-1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Hostos Community College: Discrimination, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Hunter College, 1964-1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Hunter College High School and Elementary School, 1964-1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Hunter College: Sex Discrimination, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Instructor Recruitment, ca.1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Insurance (Medical, life, etc.), 1953, 1964-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - John Jay College of Criminal Justice, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Joint Committee of Teachers Organizations, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Junior Colleges, 1968, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Kibee, Robert J. (Chancellor), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Kingsborough Community College, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - LaGuardia Community College, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Labor Caucus, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Leaflets, undated, 1960-1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Leaflets, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Leases, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Lecturers, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Legal Counsel, 1959-1961, 1963-1972 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Legislative, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Legislative, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Legislative, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Legislative, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Legislative, 1967-1971 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Legislative Conference News, 1964-1968, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Legislative Conference News (Correspondence and Miscellaneous), 1963, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Lehman College, 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Librarians, Status of, 1963-1965, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Library Association of CUNY, 1963-1972 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Manhattan Community College, 1964-1972 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Manhattan Community College: Discrimination, 1971-1972, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Marchi Bill (Elected Officials), 1966 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Master Plan, 1964, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Mayor's Committee on Management Survey, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Membership Forms and Materials, 1959-1970 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Multiple Job Regulations, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - National Education Association, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - NEA: Affiliation, etc., 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - National Labor Relations Board Decisions, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Negotiating Committee, 1967-1972 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - NYC Community College, 1964-1972 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - NYS Teachers Association, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - NYS Teachers Association: Merger, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Officers Lists, 1954-1962 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Open Admissions, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Open Meeting, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Part-time Faculty, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Pensions, 1969, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, undated, 1963, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - PSC/United Federation of College Teachers Merger, undated, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - PSC/UFCT Merger (I), 1972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - PSC/UFCT Merger (II), 1972 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Public Employment Relations Board, undated, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - PERB: Election Correspondence, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Quayle, Oliver: Opinion Survey of CUNY Faculty, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Queens College, 1954, 1963-1972 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Queens College: Discrimination, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Queensborough Community College, 1964-1972 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Queensborough Community College: Discrimination, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Registrar, 1964-1972 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - The Reporter, 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Reports, Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Representation Decisions, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Representation Elections, undated, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Representation Elections, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Representation Elections, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Research Awards/Grants, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Resolutions, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Retirement, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Rosenblatt Bill (Jury Service), 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Sabbaticals, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Salaries, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Salaries, 1935-1950 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Salaries, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Salaries, 1952-1955 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Salaries, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Salaries, 1957, 1959-1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Salaries, 1963-1968 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Salaries: Librarians, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Schools of General Studies: Contract Provisions, undated, 1969-1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Schools of General Studies: Hunter College, 1968, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Schools of General Studies: Queens College, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Schools of General Studies: Resolutions, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Schools of General Studies: "Save the SGS", 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Sex Discrimination, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Seymour Bill (Vesting), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Staff, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Staten Island Community College, 1960-1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Staten Island Community College: Sunnyside Campus Chapter, 1964, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Statistical Breakdowns for LC Members and Other Statistics, undated, 1963-1972 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Student Development Faculty, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Student Evaluation of Teaching, 1946, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Student Rights (CUNY Student Senate), 1969-1972 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Taylor Law Amendment, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Teachers Retirement System/Teachers Insurance Annuity Association, 1965-1972 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Teachers Strike, NYC, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Tenure, undated, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Testimony, 1950-1972 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Tuition Issue, 1964-1965, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Twenty-fifth Anniversary, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - UFCT Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - UFCT Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - UFCT: Schools of General Studies: Manhattan Community College, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - United Teachers of NYS, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - University Senate: Minutes, 1969-1972 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Vorhees Technical Institute, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Women Faculty: Regulations/Restrictions, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Woodburne Report on Faculty Organization Bylaws, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - York College, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Zeller, Belle: American State Legislatures, 1950-1954 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Zeller, Belle: American State Legislatures, 1955-1960 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Zeller, Belle: American State Legislatures, 1962, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Zeller, Belle: Biographical, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Zeller, Belle: Citizenship Clearing House, 1947-1957 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Zeller, Belle: Clippings, undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Zeller, Belle: Commission on the Structure of NYC Government, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, 1926-1943 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Zeller, Belle: Correspondence: Legislative, 1960, 1963-1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Zeller, Belle: Lobbying, 1945-1966 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Zeller, Belle: National Municipal League, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Zeller, Belle: NYS Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Zeller, Belle: Speeches and Writings, 1942-1972 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Zeller, Belle: TV Appearances, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Series III: Records of the Professional Staff Congress, 1926-2009
  Series III: Records of the Professional Staff Congress, includes constitutions, minutes (1972-1997), biographical files on officers and staff, files on individual chapters, CUNY budget files, extensive documentation of the New York City fiscal crisis of the mid-1970s, general correspondence, election files, publicity materials, lobbying files, and a series of files on PSC history. Also included are reference files on issues of concern to the union, such as affirmative action, open admissions, tenure quotas, collective bargaining in higher education, sex discrimination, and the role of students in university affairs. An extensive sub-series is comprised of office files of individual officers and staff members, including Aaron Alexander, Claude Campbell, Irwin Polishook, Irwin Yellowitz and Belle Zeller. Another sub-series is devoted to benefits-related files, including records of the Welfare Fund, the Pension Committee and Retirement Planning programs, as well as correspondence of staff members Clarissa Weiss and Beryl Weinberg. Also included are reference files on issues of concern to the union such as affirmative action, open admissions, tenure quotas, collective bargaining in higher education, sex discrimination, and the role of students in university affairs.
  - Subseries III:A: Constitution and Minutes, 1972-1997
    - Constitution, undated, 1973-1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Constitution, 1978-1981, 1985-1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Minutes: Administrative Council, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Minutes: Executive Council, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Minutes: Executive Council, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Minutes: Executive Council, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Minutes: Executive Council, 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Minutes: Executive Council, 1988-1997 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1974-1979 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1988- 1993 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Minutes: Delegate Assembly, 1994-1997 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Minutes: Negotiating Committee, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Minutes: Pension Committee, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Subseries III:B: Officers and Staff Files, 1926-2009
    - Sub Subseries III:B:1: Aaron Alexander Files, 1948-1997
      - Adjuncts, undated, 1973-1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Adjuncts, 1979-1983 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Adjuncts, 1984-1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Admissions, 1974, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Adult Education, undated, 1973-1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Adult Education, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Adult Education, 1983-1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Advertising Agencies, 1974-1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Advertising Campaign, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Advertising Proposal, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Agency Fee, 1971-1990 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Agreements, undated, 1969-1976 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Agreements, 1977-1984 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Agreements, 1987-1994 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Alexander, Aaron, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Alumni Studies, 1974-1978 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), undated, 1971-1981 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - AAUP, 1982, 1985-1983 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - AAUP, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - AAUP, 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - AFL-CIO (NY State & National), 1973-1978 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - AFSCME, DC 37, 1975-1986, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - American Federation of Teachers (AFT), undated, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - AFT, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - AFT: Convention, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Arbitration, undated, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Arbitration Awards, 1972-1977 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Arbitration Awards, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Arbitration Awards, 1979-1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Associations/Organizations: General, 1974-1985 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Baruch College Chapter, undated, 1970-1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Baruch College Chapter, 1980-1989 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Bio: Campbell, Claude, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Bio: Chapey, Geraldine, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Bio: Jones, Howard, 1986-1995 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Bio: Kugler, Israel, undated, 1987-1992 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Bio: Leberstein, Stephen, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Bio: Polishook, Irwin, 1985-1998 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Bio: Shanker, Albert, 1971-1989 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Bio: Starling, Marion, 1979-1994 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Bio: Yellowitz, Irwin, 1981-1987 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Bio's: Chapter Chairpersons, 1973-1992 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Bio's: Miscellaneous, 1982-1997 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Board of Higher Education, undated, 1972-1988 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC) Chapter, 1980-1985 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - BMCC Chapter, 1986-1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - BMCC: PSC Grievances, undated, 1971-1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - BMCC: PSC Grievances, 1977-1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Bronx Community College, undated, 1976-1988 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Brooklyn College, undated, 1971-1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Brooklyn College, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Brooklyn College, 1980-1984 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Brooklyn College, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Brooklyn Educational Opportunity Center, undated, 1977-1989 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Budget Constraints Survey (I), 1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Budget Constraints Survey (II), 1991 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Budget (PSC), undated, 1970-1977 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Budget (PSC), 1978-1984 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Budget (PSC), 1985-1988 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Budget (PSC), 1989-1992 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Budget Questionnaire, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Budget Questionnaire (I), 1989 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Budget Questionnaire (II), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Business and Education, undated, 1977-1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Calendar, 1970-1971, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Career Education, undated, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Central Office Chapter, 1975-1986 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Chapter Chairpersons, undated, 1967, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Chapters: Pankin Memos, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - City College, undated, 1970-1982 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - City College, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - City College: Internships in Labor Relations, 1983-1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - CUNY: Budget (III), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - CUNY: Budget (III), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - CUNY: Budget (I), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - CUNY: Budget (II), 1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - CUNY: Budget, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - CUNY Courier, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - CUNY Plans, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - CUNY Plans (I), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - CUNY Plans (II), 1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - CUNY Plans (I), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - CUNY Plans (II), 1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - CUNY Plans (I), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - CUNY Plans (II), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - CUNY Plans (I), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - CUNY Plans (II), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - CUNY Plans (I), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - CUNY Plans (II), 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - CUNY Plans, 1981-1985 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - CUNY Plans, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 16)